Prophecy Time
Come.
Where are you living?
I'm living in Sweden.
You have to live a proper life. The life you are living is not good.
Yes, man of God.
The life you are living is not good.
It's true, man of God.
You can not continue living this life.
Yes, man of God.
What's next now? Even the document you are due, you are not supposed to stay there till now.
Everything is expired, yet you are still living there.
And how can you live a life of fear? You are not free.
Yes, man of God. I have been living in Sweden. My child was taken
because they said that the way I train him is not the right way they train in Sweden.
Wait, do you listen to what I'm saying?
Yes.
I say the life you are living is bad.
Not only your child. You too you were once in a custody of security.
Yes, man of God. It's true.
And your child is there now.
They took away your child.
Yes, man of God.
That's what I am saying - the life you live. You have to change.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
People of God, Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chamaka Anodu. We come from Sweden and the child beside me is Emmanuel Anodu.
- And who is he to you?
- He is my son.
Last year was very very terrible for me. I was depressed, I became suicidal.
I was crying, I couldn't sleep, I couldn't even eat. I couldn't concentrate on my studies or on anything
because my son was taken away. So I had to come to SCOAN immediately to seek the face of God.
What do you mean by your son was taken away?
My son was taken in custody by the authorities in Sweden.
Because he was stubborn in school, so I hit him.
He went to school and told his teachers, so they took him.
So I had to run down to the SCOAN to seek the face of God.
And when I came, I was opportuned out of the many people here...
I was oppurtuned to receive the prophecy from the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua.
He explained me the root cause of my problem and I confirm the whole prophesy to be true.
And he also mentioned that your child was in custody, right?
Yes.
So after my stay in SCOAN, I went back to Sweden. We went to court again.
And when we got to the court room, we spent more than seven hours deliberating
whether they will give me this child or not. Even in the court room, I was praying,
spraying the Morning Water saying: "God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, see me through!
You are the only one that will give me victory in this case.
So after the court hearing, as I was going with the lawyer, the lawyer told me:
"You can not win this case. It very difficult for people to win cases like this."
I became scared. But I picked up courage, I said: "No, I have the God - the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
And this God is bigger than any government of the world, and I will have victory in this case."
Hallelujah! Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
A statement of faith indeed.
So after that she told me: "Let this your God save you, if He is true." I said ok.
So, a week later, she called me and said: "Congratulations."
Immediately she called me I was scared.
She said: "Congratulations, this your God has saved you. You won the case."
Let us clap for Jesus Christ!
So after prophesy I went back to Sweden. I made my life in the way God,
as man of God said in the prophesy. I made my life in the way of God.
And my academics which was not going well, started becoming very good and better.
And now I have two master's degrees - all to the Grace of God and my son is with me also.
Hallelujah! So you mean after this message of prophesy from the man of God
you went back to Sweden and the court case ended to your favour and your son was released
to you by the authorities. Is that right?
Yes. Even then that the court gave the other party three weeks to appeal this case, if they want -
but we did not hear from the other party; they didn't say anything.
And the court then gave me the instruction that I can now go and bring my son back.
I then went and brought him back.
That is why we are here today to thank the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua for restoring my life.
Because then, I was depressed, I was running mental. I didn't know what to do.
But today, I am glowing in the Lord. Thank you, God of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
Ok, now tell us, in a case like this ordinarily - how long was your son supposed to spend in custody?
My case was very controversial and very difficult.The court said my son was going to stay
with them until he was eighteen years.
And how old was your son?
He was 7 years old when he was taken.
And I don't know how I could manage it. And he would lack motherly care.
I said: "How will I manage this?" That is why I had to come.
And in these cases, a lot of people that have this problem - they have not received their children
but in my case people were asking: "What is your secret? How did you do this?"
I said: "It is the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua that did it for me."
Let's clap for Jesus Christ.
So we thank God. Can we just hear from our little brother.
Hallo. How are you?
Fine.
Tell us your name.
My name is Chisom.
And how old are you?
Eight.
And the woman standing beside you - who is she to you?
She is my mother.
Your mother. And you happy to be with your mother again?
Yes.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
So thank you, madam.We thank God Almighty for intervening in your situation.
And now that the battle is over, we want to encourage you to make God's Word a standard for your life
and to bring up your son in the way of the Lord, so that when he grows up, he will not depart from it.
And we pray that God Almighty will give you the inner grace to do so, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Shemaclatta Chiamaka. I am a Nigerian but I live in Sweden.
And the boy next to me is my son, Emmanuel Anodu.
Last year, my son was taken away by the social authorities in Sweden
because of the correction I gave to him which he went to school and reported.
And they decided that the child will not be coming back home again.
He was taken into custody and put into a foster home where he stayed for that period.
And I was not allowed to see him.
So during the period when my child was away I was depressed, I had memory loss.
I couldn't concentrate, I was devastated.
I couldn't do anything. So that was the effect that it had on me.
One of the reasons why I was devastated and depressed,
was that it was very controversial and tough case and it wasn't easy.
Regarding the type of case that it was, involving a child and abuse.
I went to different people for help and advice and they told me that there is no way out
because a lot of families have lost their kids to the social authority.
And it was very difficult for me to be able to get my son back
So I had to run down to SCOAN to seek the face of God concerning the situation.
And I was opportuned to receive a prophesy from the man of God
regarding my past life and concerning the issue of my child's case.
He told me that my son will be released and that everything will be fine.
And then I went back to Sweden.
Few weeks later, I was invited to the court in regards to the same case.
And after the court proceedings the case was judged in my favour.
And my son was released back to me. Which was a miracle.
So here I am today. I am happy, I thank God. I have my son beside me.
And everything is settled in Jesus' name.
The joy of every mother is to be with their children and my joy has been restored in Jesus' name.
Amen. We give glory to God Almighty for what He has done in your life
and rejoice for this wonderful thing that God Almighty has done.
We would like to hear a word from your son.
My name is Chisom. I am from Stockholm, Sweden.
How old are you?
8.
And who is the woman beside you?
My mum.
And how are you feeling now?
Good. I am happy to be home.
Wow! We rejoice with you that you are back home and we thank God Almighty.
We know that the best is yet to come in your lives in Jesus' name.
The only advice I have for parents who are experiencing what I have passed through
is that with God all things are possible in Jesus' name.
Amen! Indeed, with God Almighty, all things are possible.
He is the final authority, answering all questions and settling all issues.
And we know that He has settled your issues, He will also settle theirs in Jesus' name.
Amen!
So we rejoice with you once again for what God Almighty has done in your life.
And Prophet T.B.Joshua, seeing what you have been through in the past -
just like you explained you were devastated you were disturbed,
like every mother would be - man of God has sent us on behalf of himself and Emmanuel TV Partners.
He is blessing you with a sum of 150 000 Naira for the upkeep of your son.
We know that the good Lord who that started His work in your life will definitely complete it.
And we know that the best is yet to come. All you need to do is continue to walk in the light of God
and train up this child in the way of God so that as he grows up, he will not depart from it in Jesus' name.
Amen! I was not expecting this from the man of God, truly.
And I want to use this opportunity to thank man of God for the gift of the money and also of the Mirror book.
And also I want to thank man of God for his kindness, his assistance
and all the role he played during the time I ran down to SCOAN for this help.
I also want to thank man of God for the $1000 he gave to me, when I came also.
I am truly blessed with all this financial, with all the money he gave to me.
I am truly blessed. Thank you, man of God for these gifts.
Thank you for giving attention to me and for all your help and assistance.
Thank you! Thank you so much, man of God, thank you!
We thank God Almighty. Better is not good enough, the best is yet to come.
We believe that many more testimonies are to come from your family in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Receives Cash Gift Of 150 000 Naira From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
TT submitted 20/10/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 22/11/2018